

# Md. Rohul Amin

## Software Engineer

- 🗣 Sha 66/3, Shadhinata Sarani, North Badda, Gulshan, Dhaka, Bangladesh 🛗 05 Jan 1996
- 🟲 Bangladeshi 🕲 Unmarried 🛭 in radipu 🕥 radipu 😩 radipu 🔇 dipuxoo 🖼 radipu
  - radipu.me 🗲 radipu 🕕 radipu

## **CAREER OBJECTIVES**

I am experienced in leadership and both front-end and back-end programming languages. Now, I am looking for establishing my career as a .NET developer and team lead. I am a quick learner and willing to learn new technologies to upgrade myself with time. I am working with .NET technology since 2018.

# **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

Aug 2022 - present

#### **Gulf State Software**

Dhaka, Bangladesh Software Developer

- Working in Warehouse Management System.
- Working on Web and Tab Applications
- I am adding new features and debugging the existing applications.
- Technologies: C# ASP.NET, JSON, Azure DevOps, MSSQL Server, Angular, Bootstrap, Xamarin, Wpf, Crystal Reports

Jan 2022 - Jul 2022

### CureTech Ltd

Dhaka, Bangladesh

Software Engineer

- Developed web applications.
- Worked on the Engineering part of different projects.
- Lead a team.
- Technologies: C# .NET5, Angular, NodeJS, MSSQL, Laravel, MySQL, AWS, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Software Design

Aug 2021 – Jan 2022

### **Ginilab Limited**

Sunderland, England

Software Engineer 🗷

- Worked on Restaurant Management System.
- Added new features, and debugging.
- Technologies: .NET Framework, DevExpress, WinForms, Software Design, Fron-end, and Back-end.

#### Feb 2021 - Jul 2021

#### OurEdu

Dhaka, Bangladesh

Software Engineer

- Worked on Account Management System.
- Upgrading the old technology to new technology.
- Technologies: C# ASP.NET Core 3.1, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, LINQ, CSS, MSSQL, and DevOps.

## Jan 2015 - Jan 2021

## Bangladesh Study Forum (BDSF)

Dhaka, Bangladesh

Head of Information and Communication Technology ☑

- Developed the whole IT system for this organization.
- · Lead the IT team.
- What have I done: Website development, Organized programs, public speaking, Leadership.

## PROJECTS

Aug 2022 - present

## Amedig Management 2

Warehouse Management

• Technologie: Azure DevOps, .NET Framework, MSSQL Server, Angular

Feb 2022 - Jul 2022

#### Bachao 🛮

Against the rape

- It's a mobile application platform against rape.
- The backend was developed with .NET.
- Technologies: .NET5, Angular, WebAPI, MSSQL

Aug 2021 - Jan 2022

## Restaurant Management System

- It's a desktop software, mostly used in the UK and in the middle east.
- Nearly 200+ restaurants and thousands of customers use this software for ordering food inside and outside the restaurant.
- Added new features and debugging.
- Technologies: ASP.NET, DevExpress, WinForms, MySQL, Laragon, HeidiSQL

Feb 2021 - May 2021

# Account Management System for Shidlai Ashraf Secondary School

- Enroll new students with details information.
- · Adding new staff and teachers.
- Payroll and tuition fees management.
- Online payment module.
- Technologies: C#, ASP.NET Core 3.1, JavaScript, Bootstrap, CSS, jQuery, JSON, LINQ, and following Onion Architecture.

May 2019 - Aug 2019

### **Library Management System**

Technologies: C#, ASP.NET Core 2.1, Bootstrap, CSS, jQuery, JSON, LINQ.

# SKILLS

Frontend **Programming** VueJS, Angular, HTML5, Bootstrap, CSS3, Sass, Language Wpf C, C++, Java, JavaScript, C#, R, Python, **TypeScript Frameworks** .NET Core, .NET, Laravel **Backend** NodeJS **DevOps** AWS, GCP, Azure, Docker, Jenkins, Kubernetes, **Database** Bash Oracle, MySQL, MSSQL Server, PostgreSQL Data Structure and -Source Control Git, GitHub Algorithm Interpersonal skills **Cyber Security** 

Penetration, Forensics, Reverse Engineering,

Social Engineering

## **EDUCATION**

Responsibility, Teamwork

Listening, Caring, Leadership, Self-Motivated,

May 2021

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Engineering

International University of Business Agriculture and Technology
Completed BSc with a CGPA of 3.27 out of 4.00

Higher Secondary Certificate

Cambrian College
Completed HSC with a GPA of 5.00 out of 5.00

Jan 2009 - May 2011

Secondary School Certificate

Cumilla, Bangladesh

Shidlai Ashraf Secondary School
Completed SSC with a GPA of 5.00 out of 5.00

# **♂** INTERESTS

- Learning New Skills
   Public Speaking
   Reading
- Writing Leadership

# **S** LANGUAGES

Bangla • • • • English • • • •